

PROFILE

I'm a front-end web developer and graphic designer, I have passion for creating, designing and implementing responsive and user-friendly websites and applications. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and various front-end frameworks such as ReactJS, Strong understanding of web development principles, including cross-browser compatibility, web performance optimization, and accessibility. I am also well-versed in back-end technologies including PHP, and have experience with several popular database such MySQL and SQL.

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

- Project Management
- Strong decision making
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Service focused
- Innovative
- Teamwork

HOBBIES

- Graphic Design
- Learning new things
- Basketball
- Programming

NASHRUDIN N. HABIBON

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER / GRAPHICS DESIGNER

EDUCATION

Tertiary

Holy Cross of Davao College, Inc. 2015-2016 Sta. Ana Ave., Davao City 8000

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Secondary

Sta Ana National High School 2011-2012 Damosa Suazo St., Davao City 8000

Elementary

Jose P. Rizal Elementary School 2007-2008 Damosa Suazo St., Davao City 8000

EXPERIENCE

NATIONAL TELECOMMUNICATIONS COMMISSION REGION 11

OJT

March 2015 - May 2015

Assist and support regular employee team in various task such as encoding and entertaining client.

IT PERSONNEL (JOB ORDER)

June 2016 - March 2019

Maintain the database for daily operation, also encoding data of clients and processing of their licenses.

CITY GOVERNMENT OF DAVAO

AUXILARY SERVICE WORKER (IT PERSONNEL)

July 2019 – June 2023

I was deployed in NTC RXI, Maintain the database for daily operation, also encoding data of clients and processing of their licenses.

CONTACTS

PHONE: 09367034630

WEBSITE: https://nashhabibon.vercel.app

EMAIL: nashrudinhabibon@gmail.com